Guide to the Kevin Killian and Dodie Bellamy Papers
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Photographs, 1965-2012; Series VI; 13.3; (24 boxes)
  - 8x10 Photographs, 1965-2012
    - Colin Smith, undated (Box 71)
    - Dale Smith, undated (Box 71)
    - Eric Smith, undated (Box 71)
    - Jen Smith, undated (Box 71)
    - Jessica Smith, undated (Box 71)
    - Kiki Smith and Barbara Guest, undated (Box 71)
    - Logan Ryan Smith, undated (Box 71)
    - Lytton Smith, undated (Box 71)
    - Patti Smith, undated (Box 71)
    - Rod Smith and Robert Mittenthal, undated (Box 71)
    - Wayne Smith, undated (Box 71)
    - Michael Snediker, undated (Box 71)
    - Michael Smoler, undated (Box 71)
    - Dodie in the snow, undated (Box 71)
    - Eric Sneathen, undated (Box 71)
    - Rick Snyder, undated (Box 71)
    - K M Soehnlein, undated (Box 71)
    - Dennis Somera, undated (Box 71)
    - Rebecca Solnit with Jay DeFeo's painting "The Veronica", undated (Box 71)
    - Mark Soo, undated (Box 71)
    - South of Heaven by Jim Thompson (ill. Raymond Pettibon), undated (Box 71)
    - Edward Spade and Sam Gordon, undated (Box 71)
    - Juliana Spahr, undated (Box 71)
    - Tom Spanbauer, undated (Box 71)
    - Jack Spicer, by William McNeill, undated (Box 71)
    - Spicer Cake for Kevin's 53rd birthday, undated (Box 71)
    - Spicer Papers at the Bancroft Library, undated (Box 71)
    - Spicer Bust and Kevin kissing it, undated (Box 71)
    - Gareth Spor and Taha Belal, undated (Box 71)
    - Jane Sprague, undated (Box 71)
    - Justin Spring, undated (Box 71)
    - Anna Joy Springer and Ruby, undated (Box 71)
    - Annie Sprinkle, undated (Box 71)
    - Matthew and Mikko Stadler, undated (Box 71)
    - Mikko Stadler, undated (Box 71)
    - Erika Staiti, undated (Box 71)
    - George Stanley, undated (Box 71)
    - George Stanley painting, undated (Box 71)
    - Jared Stanley, undated (Box 71)
    - Frances Stark and baby Arlo, undated (Box 71)
    - Statuary at St. Patrick's Church, San Francisco, undated (Box 71)
    - Steel drums on beach in Hammond, Indiana, undated (Box 71)
    - Sue Steel, undated (Box 71)
    - Barbara Steele and Kevin Killian, photo by Dodie Bellamy, undated (Box 71)
    - Brian Kim Stefans, undated (Box 71)
    - Amelia Stein, undated (Box 71)
    - Jordan Stein, undated (Box 71)
    - Suzanne Stein, undated (Box 71)
    - Suzanne Stein and Anne Tardos, undated (Box 71)
    - Konrad Steiner, undated (Box 71)
    - Eirik Steinhoff, undated (Box 71)
    - Paul Stephens, undated (Box 71)
    - Isaac Stern, undated (Box 71)
    - James Thomas Stevens, undated (Box 71)
    - Michael Stevenson, undated (Box 71)
    - Sam Steward's decorated lampshade, undated (Box 71)
    - Nick Stillman, undated (Box 71)
    - Couple on Stilts, Minna at nth, undated (Box 71)
    - Brandon Stosuy, undated (Box 71)
    - Brian Strang, undated (Box 71)
    - Catriona Strang, undated (Box 71)
    - Peter Streckfus, undated (Box 71)
    - Jordan Strom, undated (Box 71)
    - Ben Strong, undated (Box 71)
    - Christina Strong, undated (Box 71)
    - Student of Peter's from UMass at Portland, undated (Box 71)
    - Stupid-Fake Ed Ruscha in Red Yarn, undated (Box 71)
    - Elaine Sturtevant, undated (Box 71)
    - Arthur Suits, undated (Box 71)
    - A Sun Cab by James Schuyler, undated (Box 71)
    - Elizabeth Sussman, undated (Box 71)
    - Matt Sussman, undated (Box 71)
    - Reuben Sutton, undated (Box 71)
    - CW Swets, undated (Box 71)
    - Matilda Bernstein Sycamore, undated (Box 71)
    - Chris Sylvester as Kurt Russell, Buffalo 2009 (Box 71)
    - Sylvia, October 2005, 2005 October (Box 71)
    - Sylvia, May 2006, 2006 May (Box 71)
    - Sylvia, February 2007, 2007 February (Box 71)
    - Sylvia, September 2008, 2008 September (Box 71)
    - Zak Szymanski, undated (Box 71)
    - Stacy Szymaszek, undated (Box 71)
    - Tina Tahir at UIC, undated (Box 71)
    - T'ai Chi Master, undated (Box 71)
    - Take a Step Back and View the Sentence (KK installation at SF Camerawork, January 2010), 2010 January (Box 71)
    - Abdellah Taia, undated (Box 71)
    - Abdellah Taia and Hedi El Khouti, undated (Box 71)
    - Ellen Tallman, undated (Box 71)
    - Karen Tallman, undated (Box 71)
    - Meredith Talusan, undated (Box 71)
    - Curtains in Sikay Tang's apartment, undated (Box 71)
    - Lexander Tanz, undated (Box 71)
    - MarkTardi, undated (Box 71)
    - Anne Tardos, undated (Box 71)
    - Garrison Taylor, undated (Box 71)
    - Justin Taylor, undated (Box 71)
    - Joan Taylor, undated (Box 71)
    - Michelle Tea, undated (Box 71)
    - Lisa Teasley, undated (Box 72)
    - Ted February 2007, 2007 February (Box 72)
    - Margaret Tedesco, undated (Box 72)
    - Roberto Tejada, undated (Box 72)
    - Fiona Templeton, undated (Box 72)
    - Gabrielle Teschner, undated (Box 72)
    - Althea Thauberger, undated (Box 72)
    - Lena Thayer, undated (Box 72)
    - Ryan Thayer, undated (Box 72)
    - Elizabeth Thomas, undated (Box 72)
    - Elizabeth Thomas and Joseph del Pesco, undated (Box 72)
    - Hank Willis Thomas, "Gold Dust Twins", undated (Box 72)
    - Lorenzo Thomas, undated (Box 72)
    - Jeremy James Thompson, undated (Box 72)
    - Dan Thomas-Quick, undated (Box 72)
    - Skye Thorstenson, undated (Box 72)
    - Daniel Tiffany, undated (Box 72)
    - Lynne Tillman, undated (Box 72)
    - Parker Tilghman, undated (Box 72)
    - Parker Tilghman and Daniel Nicoletta, undated (Box 72)
    - Meg Tilly, undated (Box 72)
    - Matthew Timmons, undated (Box 72)
    - Math Tinder, undated (Box 72)
    - Tino Sehgal piece, guards of different races kissing, undated (Box 72)
    - Hayley Tompkins, undated (Box 72)
    - Miranda Torn, undated (Box 72)
    - Tony Torn and Lee Ann Brown, undated (Box 72)
    - Edwin Torres, undated (Box 72)
    - Rodrigo Toscano, undated (Box 72)
    - Town Hall of Basel, undated (Box 72)
    - Amy Trachtenberg, undated (Box 72)
    - Peter Trachtenberg, undated (Box 72)
    - Truong Tran, undated (Box 72)
    - Scott Treleaven and Paul P. (photographed by Dodie Bellamy), undated (Box 72)
    - Siren Trimane, Portland's best Kylie impersonator, undated (Box 72)
    - David Trinidad, undated (Box 72)
    - Quincy Troupe, undated (Box 72)
    - Christopher Trout, undated (Box 72)
    - HungQ. Tu, undated (Box 72)
    - Zachary Darr Tuck and Jacqueline Frost, undated (Box 72)
    - Marie Tuohey-Mote, undated (Box 72)
    - Michael Turner, undated (Box 72)
    - King Tut souvenirs, LACMA, July 2005, 2005 July (Box 72)
    - LucTuymans, undated (Box 72)
    - TV Sutras, undated (Box 72)
    - 25th Anniversary, Caffe Macaroni, July 2on, photos by Karla Milosevich, undated (Box 72)
    - Bracelet of Joe Tynan, undated (Box 72)
    - Chris Tysh, undated (Box 72)
    - Kota Uetsu, undated (Box 72)
    - David Ulin, undated (Box 72)
    - Underwear Scene from "Too Far", undated (Box 72)
    - Neil Uzzell, undated (Box 72)
    - Jeffrey Vallance, undated (Box 72)
    - Paul Van De Carr, undated (Box 72)
    - Marcus Vater and Sophie von Hellerman, undated (Box 72)
    - Vegetable Kingdom at Art Basel 38: Barry Schwabsky, Marie-Laure de Beausacq, Michele de Menna, Chris Johanson, undated (Box 72)
    - Torbjom Vejvi, undated (Box 72)
    - Divya Victor, undated (Box 72)
    - Divya Victor as Courtney Love, Buffalo 2009 (Box 72)
    - Aaron Vidaver, undated (Box 72)
    - Matias Viegener, undated (Box 74)
    - Oscar Villalon, undated (Box 72)
    - Benjamin Vilmain, undated (Box 72)
    - Jonathan Viner, undated (Box 72)
    - Gerald Vizenor, undated (Box 72)
    - Karen Volkmann, undated (Box 72)
    - Tris Vonna-Michell, undated (Box 72)
    - Valerie Wade, undated (Box 72)
    - Catherine Wagner, undated (Box 72)
    - The other Catherine Wagner, undated (Box 72)
    - James Wagner, undated (Box 72)
    - The Filming of Wagner Ross, undated (Box 72)
    - Christopher Wagstaff, undated (Box 72)
    - Fred Wah, undated (Box 72)
    - Anne Waldman, undated (Box 72)
    - Walgreens Montage, undated (Box 72)
    - Kara Walker and Rabih Alameddine, undated (Box 72)
    - Wall photo (of Kevin by Job Piston), undated (Box 72)
    - Jonathan Wallraven, undated (Box 72)
    - Anne Walsh, undated (Box 72)
    - Shanxing Wang, undated (Box 72)
    - Dana Ward and Alli Warren, undated (Box 72)
    - Diane Ward, undated (Box 72)
    - Greg Ware, undated (Box 72)
    - John Francis Warner, undated (Box 72)
    - Alli Warren, undated (Box 72)
    - Patricia Nell Warren, undated (Box 72)
    - Watermelon+ Shoes (Colter Jacobsen, Sara Larsen, Dodie B., and Kevin K.), undated (Box 72)
    - Don Waters, undated (Box 72)
    - Jacqueline Waters, undated (Box 72)
    - John Waters, undated (Box 74)
    - Mitchell Watkins, undated (Box 72)
    - Scott Watson, undated (Box 72)
    - Steven Watson, undated (Box 72)
    - Susan Watson and Kenward Elmslie, undated (Box 72)
    - Rebecca Weaver, undated (Box 72)
    - Bobbie "Spider" Webb, undated (Box 72)
    - Noura Wedell, undated (Box 72)
    - Laurie Weeks, undated (Box 72)
    - Charles Weigl, undated (Box 72)
    - Don Weise, undated (Box 72)
    - Karen Weiser, undated (Box 72)
    - Karen Weiser and her daughter Sylvie, undated (Box 72)
    - Frances Weiss, undated (Box 72)
    - Jono Weiss, undated (Box 72)
    - ruth weiss, undated (Box 72)
    - Benjamin Weissman, undated (Box 72)
    - Bernard Welt, undated (Box 72)
    - Darren Wershler-Henry, undated (Box 72)
    - Christine Wertheim, undated (Box 72)
    - Joel Westendorf, undated (Box 73)
    - Joe Westmoreland and Charles Atlas, undated (Box 73)
    - Greg Wharton and Ian Philips, undated (Box 73)
    - Liz Wheeler, undated (Box 73)
    - White Columns Show, NYC, February 2006, 2006 February (Box 73)
    - Ed White, undated (Box 73)
    - White Rabbits: Nick Laesing, Andre Niebur, Markus Yater, undated (Box 73)
    - Brian Whitener, undated (Box 73)
    - David Whitney and Kevin Killian, undated (Box 73)
    - Zoe Whittall, undated (Box 73)
    - Chet Wiener, undated (Box 73)
    - Actors in John Wieners' "Asphodel" play at Small Press Traffic, undated (Box 73)
    - January 2006, photos by Mike Palmieri, 2006 January (Box 73)
    - Will (Uk translatior), undated (Box 73)
    - Chet Williams, undated (Box 73)
    - Michael Williams (Don Allen's attorney), undated (Box 73)
    - Tyrone Williams, undated (Box 73)
    - Elizabeth Willis, undated (Box 73)
    - Emily Wilson and Minette Lehmann, undated (Box 73)
    - Ronald V. Wilson, undated (Box 73)
    - Jim Winters and his portrait by Jason Meder, undated (Box 73)
    - Jim Winters' "Parakeet Attack" at Ratio 3, undated (Box 73)
    - Sara Wintz, undated (Box 73)
    - Alan Witchey, undated (Box 73)
    - Wizard of Oz confetti at Wattis Institute, September 2008, 2008 September (Box 73)
    - David Michael Wolach, undated (Box 73)
    - Allyssa Wolf, undated (Box 73)
    - Ed Wolf, undated (Box 73)
    - Manfred Wolf, undated (Box 73)
    - Matt Wolf, undated (Box 73)
    - Tobias Wolff, undated (Box 73)
    - Melissa Wolsak, undated (Box 73)
    - Lebbeus Woods, undated (Box 73)
    - Erwin Wulf, undated (Box 73)
    - B. Wurtz, undated (Box 73)
    - Lynn Xu, undated (Box 73)
    - Will Yackulic, undated (Box 73)
    - Torno Yasuda, undated (Box 73)
    - Amanda Yates, undated (Box 73)
    - Katie Yates, undated (Box 73)
    - Jonathan Yegge, undated (Box 73)
    - Heriberto Yepes, undated (Box 73)
    - Al Young, undated (Box 73)
    - Alex Young, undated (Box 73)
    - Stephanie Young, undated (Box 73)
    - Youth bas-relief in Berkeley, undated (Box 73)
    - Timothy Yu, undated (Box 73)
    - Matt Szapruder, undated (Box 73)
    - Jery Zaslove, undated (Box 73)
    - Sharon Zetter, undated (Box 73)
    - Jake Ziemann, undated (Box 73)
    - Philip Zimbardo, undated (Box 73)
    - Zine signage for Kiki show by Colter Jacobsen, undated (Box 73)
    - Slavoz Zizek, undated (Box 73)
    - Rachel Zolf, undated (Box 73)
    - Steve Zultanbski as Dr. Tim Baldwin, Buffalo 2009 (Box 73)
    - Maggie Zurawski, undated (Box 73)
    - Jason Zuzga, undated (Box 73)
    - Unidentified, undated (Box 73)
  - Tagged, undated; 5 (Box 75)
    Kevin Killian's photographs of (mostly nude) men posing with a drawing of male genitalia by Raymond Pettibon. Photographed as Killian's "investigation of masculinity and how the visible signs of our gender don't necessarily dictate what lies beneath, within, ahead."
  - General photographs, 1999-2009
    General photographs consist of 4x6 photographs, mostly housed in the original printing envelopes. Most envelopes are labelled with identifying information. Some negatives included. Some envelopes also contain photo CDs.
    - Photographs, 1999; 14 (Box 76)
    - Photographs, 2000; 10 (Box 76)
    - Photographs, 2001; 14 (Box 77)
    - Photographs, 2002; 8 (Box 77)
    - Photographs, 2003; 9 (Box 77)
    - Photographs, 2004; 19 (Box 78)
    - Photographs, 2005; 14 (Box 78)
    - Photographs, 2005; 19 (Box 79)
    - Photographs, 2006; 16 (Box 79)
    - Photographs, 2006; 22 (Box 80)
    - Photographs, 2007; 26 (Box 80)
    - Photographs, 2008; 42 (Box 81)
    - Photographs, 2009; 7 (Box 81)
    - Photographs, undated; 11 (Box 82)
    - Small press distribution canvas bag, undated (Box 82)
- Audiovisual materials, 1977-2012; Series VII; 1.63; (3 boxes)
  Conditions Governing Access
  Restricted fragile material. Reference copies may be requested. Consult Access Services for further information.
  - Fifth Column/Trailer Queen, "I Love You, But…" and "These Boots Were Made 4 Walking", undated; 1 (Box 83)
    45 RPM record
  - Ladytron, "Blue Jeans", 2003; 1 (Box 83)
  - Gio Black Peter, "The Virgin Shuffle" and "I Got No Strings", 2011; 2 (Box 83)
  - Fifth Column, "Signs of Things to Come", undated; 1 (Box 83)
  - Johnny Jingo/Jeepers Creepers, undated; 1 (Box 83)
  - John Waters Interview (audiocassette), 2001 August 03; 1 (Box 83, Item barcode 39002099364607)
  - The Die Ads "eighty-eight feet high", 2012; 1 (Box 83)
  - Big Joy, The Adventures of James Broughton, undated; 1 (Box 83)
  - blondie "Plastic Letters", 1977; 1 (Box 83)
  - Reader Interviews, 5; 2 (Box 83)
    Audiovisual material. Restricted fragile. Reference copies may be requested. Consult Access Services for more information.
    - Lisa, 1995 March 26; 1 (Box 83, Item barcode 39002099364615)
    - Margo & Nita (1 of 2 audiocassettes), 1995 March 25; 1 (Box 83, Item barcode 39002099364631)
    - Margo & Nita (2 of 2 audiocassettes), undated; 1 (Box 83, Item barcode 39002099364623)
    - Will & Erizen, 1995 July 15 and 16; 1 (Box 83, Item barcode 39002099364649)
    - Lauren, 1995 March 25; 1 (Box 83, Item barcode 39002099364656)
  - Harry's House, 2012; 1 (Box 83)
  - Harry's House Vol II, undated; 1 (Box 84)
  - Kevin McMahon, 1994 December 16; 1 (Box 84, Item barcode 39002099364680)
  - Charles Richards, 1994 December 14; 1 (Box 84, Item barcode 39002099364698)
  - David Lane (1 of 2 audiocassettes), 1994 December 15; 1 (Box 84, Item barcode 39002099364664)
  - David Lane (2 of 2 audiocassettes), 1994 December 17; 1 (Box 84, Item barcode 39002104619953)
  - David Lane, 1995 February 11; 1 (Box 84, Item barcode 39002099364672)
  - Interview for Jack Spicer bio and miscellaneous audiocassettes, 112; 1 (Box 85)
    Audiovisual material. Restricted fragile. Reference copies may be requested. Consult Access Services for further information.
    - Barney, 1980 April 10; 1 (Box 85, Item barcode 39002099363476)
    - Debbie 1 / Debbie 2, undated; 1 (Box 85, Item barcode 39002099363492)
    - Voice, Debbie 3, undated; 1 (Box 85, Item barcode 39002099363484)
    - David Bromige Interview in Sebastopol, CA, 1991 July 13; 1 (Box 85, Item barcode 39002099363500)
    - Winnie & Barney, 1980 April 10; 1 (Box 85, Item barcode 39002099363518)
    - Discussing Spicer Bio, 1999 March 18; 1 (Box 85, Item barcode 39002099363526)
    - Thomas Evans Interview, 1993 May 21; 1 (Box 85, Item barcode 39002099363534)
    - Manfred Wolf interviewed by KK and Lew Ellingham in SF, 2007 March 19; 1 (Box 85, Item barcode 39002099363542)
    - Karen Tallman DeBeck by Kevin Killian, Vancouver, 1992 May 24; 1 (Box 85, Item barcode 39002099363559)
    - R.T., SPT / Same as A. Rodrigo Toscano, undated; 1 (Box 85, Item barcode 39002099363567)
    - #350 copy, Robin Blaser reading works by Jack Spicer & himself, 1967 March 9; 1 (Box 85, Item barcode 39002099363575)
    - Warren Tallman interview #2, 1991 April 5; 1 (Box 85, Item barcode 39002099363583)
    - Mary Harron, 2001 August 20, August 22; 1 (Box 85, Item barcode 39002099363591)
    - Michael Davidson, UCSD, 1994 August 1; 1 (Box 85, Item barcode 39002099363609)
    - San [Francisco] Marathon @ Hill St., 1999 March 20; 1 (Box 85, Item barcode 39002099363617)
      Reading at Paula Lu's include: Yedda Morrison, Kevin Killian, d. Bellamy, Jen Hofer, R. Gladman, and Lauran Coudath.
    - Allen Ginsberg Interview, undated; 1 (Box 85, Item barcode 39002099363625)
    - The New Design Gallery, Vancouver / Berkeley: Summer Days / Language, 1965 June, July; 1 (Box 85, Item barcode 39002099363633)
      Speakers include: Jack Spicer, Robin Blaser, and Stan Persky.
    - "Magic Workshop", 1987 June 10; 1 (Box 85, Item barcode 39002099363641)
      Included are readings by: B. Conner, E. Boraguard, H. Adam, R. Duneaun, J. Dunn, J. Spicer.
    - Robin Blaser in conversation with Jack Foley, Oakland (1 of 2 audiocassettes), 1994 June 8; 1 (Box 85, Item barcode 39002099363658)
    - Robin Blaser in conversation with Jack Foley, Oakland (1 of 2 audiocassettes), 1994 June 8; 1 (Box 85, Item barcode 39002099363682)
      This audiocassette aopears to be a duplicate.
    - Robin Blaser in conversation with Jack Foley, Oakland (2 of 2 audiocassettes), 1994 June 8; 1 (Box 85, Item barcode 39002099363997)
    - San Francisco / New York, 1999 March 20, April 12; 1 (Box 85, Item barcode 39002099363666)
      Contents include: Pamela Lu, Dodie Ballamy, M. Zurawski - Radio Free Woolworth's, Dan Farrell reading at the Poetry Project.
    - Rebecca Solnit Interview, undated; 1 (Box 85, Item barcode 39002099363674)
    - Maxine Gadd interviewed by Kevin Killian, Vancouver, 1992 May 25; 1 (Box 85, Item barcode 39002099363690)
    - Nicola Tyson interview, 1993 December 14; 1 (Box 85, Item barcode 39002099363708)
    - "Cry" by Johnnie Ray, undated; 1 (Box 85, Item barcode 39002099363716)
    - Anne Sexton & Her Kind at De Cordora, First Public Concert, undated; 1 (Box 85, Item barcode 39002099363724)
    - John Norton interview, undated; 1 (Box 85, Item barcode 39002099363732)
    - John Waters, undated; 1 (Box 85, Item barcode 39002099363740)
    - Bo Huston interview, 1992 December 27; 1 (Box 85, Item barcode 39002099363757)
    - Daniel Davidson interviewing Fiona Templeton, 1992 September 4; 1 (Box 85, Item barcode 39002099363765)
    - John Wieners reads, Brown University, 1995 March 14; 1 (Box 85, Item barcode 39002099363799)
      A note on the cassette reads: For Dodie + Kevin - Love, Maggie
    - Kevin Killian at writer's house, undated; 1 (Box 85, Item barcode 39002099363807)
    - Kim / Magee Oberlin Blestone reading, "Eye for One", Open House / Tarn + Duncan, Olson BBC interview, 1995 January 27; 1 (Box 85, Item barcode 39002099363815)
    - Mary Rice Moore interview, 1991 June 23; 1 (Box 85, Item barcode 39002099363823)
    - Ellen Tallman interviewed, 1991 July 3; 1 (Box 85, Item barcode 39002099363831)
    - Dick Deering intervewed by Kevin Killian, San Francisco, 1998 December 14; 1 (Box 85, Item barcode 39002099363849)
    - Bookworm: Dodie Bellamy, undated; 1 (Box 85, Item barcode 39002099363856)
    - Pettibon - Bellamy interview, Berkeley, 1992 August 30; 1 (Box 85, Item barcode 39002099363864)
    - Lyn Hejinian, 1994 August 30; 1 (Box 85, Item barcode 39002099363872)
    - Paul Alexander interviewd by Lewis Ellingham, Pt. Cabrillo, CA, 1997 April 8; 1 (Box 85, Item barcode 39002099363880)
    - Harris Schiff interview, 1991 May; 1 (Box 85, Item barcode 39002099363898)
    - Stuart Loomis interviewed by KK, San Francisco, Side 3, 1995 July 9; 1 (Box 85, Item barcode 39002099363906)
    - Josephine Fredman Stewart interview, cafe Ariel, Berkeley, 1992 March 8; 1 (Box 85, Item barcode 39002099363914)
    - Spicer, Vancouver lecture #2, undated; 1 (Box 85, Item barcode 39002099363922)
    - Nemi Frost interviewed by K. Killian, San Francisco, 1993 August 7; 1 (Box 85, Item barcode 39002099363930)
    - Richard Tagett Interview, 1991 October 27; 1 (Box 85, Item barcode 39002099363948)
    - Minnette Lehmann Interview, 1991 May 5; 1 (Box 85, Item barcode 39002099363955)
    - Dora Fitzgerald interviewed by Kevin Killian, Vancouver, 1992 May 24; 1 (Box 85, Item barcode 39002099363963)
    - Wesley Day Interview, undated; 1 (Box 85, Item barcode 39002099363971)
    - Nayland Blake and Larry Rinder interview by K. Killian, 1994 November 20; 1 (Box 85, Item barcode 39002099364003)
    - Robert Duncan on Jack Spicer, San Francisco, 1990 April 13; 1 (Box 85, Item barcode 39002099364011)
    - Chris Dewdrey talk, San Francisco, 1978 March 2; 1 (Box 85, Item barcode 39002099364029)
    - "20 Questions: A Wake-Up Call with Sandra Bullock" / Flipper - "Sex Bomb", "Life", undated; 1 (Box 85, Item barcode 39002099364037)
    - Jim Townsend interviewed, 1991 June 22; 1 (Box 85, Item barcode 39002099364045)
    - Warren Tallman Interview, 1991 January; 1 (Box 85, Item barcode 39002099364052)
    - Gerald Fabian interviewed by Kevin Killian, side 1 of 3, 1993 July 19; 1 (Box 85, Item barcode 39002099364060)
    - Gerald Fabian interviewed by Kevin Killian, side 3 of 3, 1993 July 19; 1 (Box 85, Item barcode 39002099364086)
    - Ed White - Talk to Dodie, undated; 1 (Box 85, Item barcode 39002099364094)
    - Ida Hodes interviewed by Kevin Killian, San Francisco, undated; 1 (Box 85, Item barcode 39002099364102)
    - Brian 1, undated; 1 (Box 85, Item barcode 39002099364110)
    - Ariel + Thomas Parkinson interviewed by Len Ellingham + Kevin Killian, 1991 June 22; 1 (Box 85, Item barcode 39002099364128)
    - John Allen Ryan interviewed by Kevin Killian, San Francisco, 1992 May 31; 1 (Box 85, Item barcode 39002099364136)
    - Gerald M Ackerman Interview, 1991 November 6; 1 (Box 85, Item barcode 39002099364144)
    - Robin Blaser interviewed by Kevin Killian, Vancouver, 1992 May 22; 1 (Box 85, Item barcode 39002099364151)
    - Michael McClure interviewed by Kevin Killian, Oakland, 1992 July 19; 1 (Box 85, Item barcode 39002099364169)
    - Philip Whalen interview, 1991 November 5; 1 (Box 85, Item barcode 39002099364177)
    - Myrsam Wixman interviewed by KK, sides 1 + 2 (1 of 2 audiocassettes), 1994 April 2; 1 (Box 85, Item barcode 39002099364243)
    - Myrsam Wixman interviewed by Kevin Killiam, sides 3 + 4 (2 of 2 audiocassettes), 1994 April 2; 1 (Box 85, Item barcode 39002099364185)
    - Interview with Judy Graham by Steve Abbott + Dodie Bellamy, undated; 1 (Box 85, Item barcode 39002099364193)
    - "Fruit Punch", Real: Letters of M. Harker + S. D'Allesandro, 1994 November 30; 1 (Box 85, Item barcode 39002099364201)
      Also included: Dodie Bellamy, Kevink Killian with David Lamble.
    - Larry Fagin interviewed by Kevin Killian, 1993 September 12; 1 (Box 85, Item barcode 39002099364219)
    - Lewis Warsh interviewed by Kevin Killian, NYC, 1994 September 30; 1 (Box 85, Item barcode 39002099364227)
    - Gaby Onderwyzer Stuart interviewed by Kevin Killian, Los Angeles, 1993 December 17; 1 (Box 85, Item barcode 39002099364235)
    - Lewis Ellingham interviews Myrsam Wixman, Berkeley, CA, 1997 April 17; 1 (Box 85, Item barcode 39002099364250)
    - Kevin Killian "On Spicer" (KSW), Vancouver, [British Columbia], 1991 July 6; 1 (Box 85, Item barcode 39002099364268)
    - Eileen Kaufman interviewed by Kevin Killian, San Francisco, 1994 October 9; 1 (Box 85, Item barcode 39002099364276)